advanceseooptimization.blogspot.com 2014-06-28

# SEO Internet Marketing Blog: Privacy

###  Privacy 

We respect your privacy and we’re committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at [advanceseooptimization.blogspot.com](http://advanceseooptimization.blogspot.com/). The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

**Log Files :**  
Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**E-mail Subscription :**  
If a user/reader wishes to subscribe to our posts via e-mail (powered by FeedBurner), we ask for contact information such as email address. Out of respect for our usersâ€™ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

**Cookies :**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the userâ€™s computer tied to information about the user. Our site use cookies for tracking visitorsâ€™ activity. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies foradvertising.

**Links :**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit .

**Third Party Cookies**  
Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  
**  
****Changes To Our Privacy Policy**  
To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we reserve the right to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice to or the consent of any person. Any changes or replacement will be posted at this site. **  
**  
**Contact Information :**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us by filling up the [contact form](http://advanceseooptimization.blogspot.com/p/about-us.html).
